const questionBank = [
  {
    id: 1,
    type: "mcq",
    question: "Which of the following sounds do you hear?",
    answers: ["おまえ", "たべる"],
    correctAnswer: "おまえ",
    audio: "/mp3/お前【おまえ】.mp3"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    type: "mcq",
    question: "Which of the following sounds do you hear?",
    answers: ["かんじ", "にんげん"],
    correctAnswer: "かんじ",
    audio: "/mp3/漢字【かんじ】.mp3"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    type: "mcq",
    question: "Which of the following sounds do you hear?",
    answers: ["われる", "わかる"],
    correctAnswer: "わかる",
    audio: "/mp3/分かる【わかる】.mp3"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    type: "mcq",
    question: "Which of the following sounds do you hear?",
    answers: ["かく", "がまん"],
    correctAnswer: "がまん",
    audio: "/mp3/我慢【がまん】.mp3"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    type: "mcq",
    question: "Which of the following sounds do you hear?",
    answers: ["じょうし", "じょし"],
    correctAnswer: "じょし",
    audio: "/mp3/女子【じょし】.mp3"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    type: "mcq",
    question: "Which of the following sounds do you hear?",
    answers: ["こうこう", "ここ"],
    correctAnswer: "こうこう",
    audio: "/mp3/高校【こうこう】.mp3"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    type: "mcq",
    question: "Which of the following sounds do you hear?",
    answers: ["びっと", "ひと", "きっと", "いと"],
    correctAnswer: "ひと",
    audio: "/mp3/人【ひと】.mp3"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    type: "mcq",
    question: "Which of the following sounds do you hear?",
    answers: ["おきる", "おこる", "おかす", "おこす"],
    correctAnswer: "おこす",
    audio: "/mp3/起こす【おこす】.mp3"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Using hiragana, type out the word you hear:",
    type: "frq",
    answers: ["", ""],
    correctAnswer: "ありがとう",
    audio: "/mp3/有り難う【ありがとう】.mp3"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Using hiragana, type out the word you hear:",
    type: "frq",
    answers: ["", ""],
    correctAnswer: "しゃかい",
    audio: "/mp3/社会【しゃかい】.mp3"
  },
];
export default questionBank;
